A Guide to the Office of the Vice-President, Louis A. Pardue Records, 1950-1963
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Questionnaires, General, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 229)
- Questionnaires, Junior Colleges in Virginia, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 230)
- Questionnaires, from VPI, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 231)
- R, General, 1952-1955 (Box 7, Folder 232)
- Residence Program, 1954-1955 (Box 7, Folder 233)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (5 folders) (Box 7, Folder 234a-e)
- Southern Regional Education Board (3 folders), 1955 (Box 7, Folder 235a-c)
- Statistics-Harshbarger, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 236)
- Student Activities Committee, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 237)
- Student Life Regulation Committee, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 238)
- T, General, 1953-1955 (Box 8, Folder 239)
- University Contract with Foreign Universities, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 240)
- Veterinary Medicine Selection Committee, 1953-1955 (Box 8, Folder 241)
- Virginia Advisory Committee on Schools and Colleges, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 242)
- Vocational Education-Sanders, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 243)
- A, General, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 244)
- Accreditation, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 245)
- Admissions Office-Farrier, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 246)
- Aeronautical Engineering-Truitt, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 247)
- Agriculture-Dietrick, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 248)
- Agricultural Economics-Love, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 249)
- Agronomy-Dunton, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 250)
- American Association of School Administrators, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 251)
- American Council on Education, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 252)
- Applied Mechanics, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 253)
- Applied Science and Business Administration-Johnston, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 254)
- Architecture-Cowgill, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 255)
- Association of Land-Grant Colleges and Universities, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 256)
- Association of Virginia Colleges, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 257)
- Business Administration-Knote, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 258)
- Business Manager-Cassell, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 259)
- C, General, 1954-1956 (Box 8, Folder 260)
- Conference of Deans of Southern Graduate Schools (2 folders), 1956 (Box 8, Folder 261a-b)
- D, General, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 262)
- Dairy Husbandry-Graf, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 263)
- E, General, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 264)
- Electrical Engineering-Murray, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 265)
- Engineering and Architecture-Whittemore, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 266)
- English and Foreign Language-Harrison, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 267)
- Extension Cooperative Training, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 268)
- Extension Service, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 269)
- F, General, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 270)
- Faculty Appointments, Applied Science and Business Administration, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 271)
- Faculty Listing, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 272)
- Faculty Promotions, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 273)
- Faculty Resignations, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 274)
- G, General, 1952-1956 (Box 8, Folder 275)
- Geology-Cooper, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 276)
- Graduate Assistantships, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 277)
- Graduate Faculty, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 278)
- Graduate School, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 279)
- Graduate Questionnaires, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 280)
- Guidance and Placement-Cato, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 281)
- Home Economics-Tate, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 282)
- Horticulture-Judkins, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 283)
- I, General, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 284)
- Invitations, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 285)
- Leaves of Absence, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 286)
- Marshall College, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 287)
- Mathematics-Hatcher, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 288)
- Mechanical Engineering-Jones, 1952-1956 (Box 9, Folder 289)
- Military (2 folders), 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 920a-b)
- Military, Air Force, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 291)
- Military Colleges Association, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 292)
- Mimeographs, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 293)
- N, General, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 294)
- National Education Association, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 295)
- National Science Foundation, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 296)
- News Releases and Speech Materials, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 297)
- North Carolina State College, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 298)
- North Georgia College, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 299)
- Philosophy and Religion, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 300)
- Physical Education-Younger, 1950-1956 (Box 9, Folder 301)
- Physics, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 302)
- Plant Pathology and Physiology, 1953-1956 (Box 9, Folder 303)
- Poultry Husbandry-Dietrick, 1952-1956 (Box 9, Folder 304)
- President-Newman, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 305)
- Public Relations-McNeil, 1952-1956 (Box 9, Folder 306)
- Questionnaires (2 folders), 1956 (Box 9, Folder 307a-b)
- Radford College-Martin, 1953-1956 (Box 9, Folder 308)
- S, General, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 309)
- Salaries, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 310a-b)
- Scholarship Committee, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 311)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (2 folders), 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 312a-b)
- Southern Regional Education Board (2 folders), 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 913a-b)
- Statistics-Harshbarger, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 314)
- Student Activities, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 315)
- Summer School, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 316)
- Survival Plan, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 317)
- Technical Institutes, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 318)
- Training Program, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 319)
- Virginia Advisory Committee on Schools, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 320)
- Virginia Educational Association, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 321)
- VPI Athletic Council, 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 322)
- Vocational Education, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 323)
- A, General, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 324)
- Academic Council, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 325)
- Accreditation, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 326)
- Agriculture-Dietrick, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 328)
- Agriculture Engineering-Swink, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 329)
- Agriculture Extension Station-Young, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 330)
- Agronomy, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 331)
- American Association of University Professors, 1953-1957 (Box 10, Folder 332)
- American Council on Education, 1956-1957 (Box 10, Folder 333)
- Animal Husbandry, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 334)
- Applications, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 335)
- Applied Mechanics, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 336)
- Applied Science and Business Administration, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 337)
- Architecture, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 338)
- Business Manager-Cassell, 1955-1957 (Box 10, Folder 339)
- D, General, 1955-1957 (Box 10, Folder 340)
- Danville Branch, 1955-1957 (Box 10, Folder 341)
- Faculty Appointments, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 342a-c)
- Faculty Committees, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 343)
- Faculty Listing, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 344)
- Faculty Leaves of Absence, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 345)
- Faculty Merit Increases, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 346)
- Faculty Promotions, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 347a-c)
- Faculty Resignations and Retirements, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 348)
- Geological Sciences, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 349)
- Georgia, University of, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 350)
- Grade Percentages, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 351)
- Graduate Assistantships, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 352)
- Governor's Committee on Employment of the Physically Handicapped, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 353)
- H, General, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 354)
- Higher Education, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 355)
- Home Economics, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 356)
- Improving Instruction, 1956-1957 (Box 10, Folder 357)
- Industrial Engineering, 1956-1957 (Box 10, Folder 358)
- Institute of International Education, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 359)
- Invitations, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 360)
- Jamestown Festival, 1956-1957 (Box 10, Folder 361)
- Land-Grant Colleges, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 362)
- Library, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 363)
- Manual Arts Therapy, 1955-1957 (Box 10, Folder 364)
- Mechanical Engineering-Jones, 1956-1957 (Box 10, Folder 365)
- Metallurgy-Nevitt, 1955-1957 (Box 10, Folder 366)
- Military-Devine, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 367)
- N, General, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 368)
- National Science Foundation, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 369)
- Nuclear Energy, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 370)
- O, General, 1955-1957 (Box 10, Folder 371)
- P, General, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 372)
- Parking and Traffic Committee, 1955-1957 (Box 10, Folder 373)
- Personnel-Evans, 1955-1957 (Box 10, Folder 374)
- Physics-Hahn, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 375)
- President-Newman, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 376)
- Public Relations, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 377)
- Questionnaires (5 folders), 1957 (Box 11, Folder 378a-e)
- Regional Advisory Council on Nuclear Energy (4 folder), 1957 (Box 11, Folder 379a-d)
- Registrar-Slusher, 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 380)
- Research Assistants, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 381)
- Rural Sociology-Tate, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 382)
- S, General, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 383)
- Scholarships, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 384)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (4 folders), 1957 (Box 11, Folder 385a-d)
- Southern Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 386)
- Southern Graduate Deans, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 387)
- Southern Regional Conference, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 388)
- Committee Meetings (4 folders), 1957 (Box 11, Folder 389a-d)
- State Board of Education, 1954-1957 (Box 11, Folder 390)
- State Council of Higher Education, 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 391)
- Statistics-Harshbarger, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 392)
- Student Activities Committee, 1954-1957 (Box 11, Folder 393)
- Students and Their Families, 1954-1957 (Box 11, Folder 394)
- Summer School, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 395)
- Tau Beta Pi, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 396)
- Technical Institutes, 1955-1957 (Box 12, Folder 397)
- U, General, 1953-1957 (Box 12, Folder 398)
- V, General, 1950-1957 (Box 12, Folder 399)
- Virginia Advisory Legislature Council, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 400)
- Virginia College Associations, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 401)
- VPI Alumni Association, 1955-1957 (Box 12, Folder 402)
- VPI Educational Foundation-Hutcheson, 1955-1957 (Box 12, Folder 403)
- Vocational Education, 1954-1957 (Box 12, Folder 404)
- W, General, 1954-1957 (Box 12, Folder 405)
- YMCA, 1952-1957 (Box 12, Folder 406)
- A, General, 1952-1958 (Box 12, Folder 407)
- Academic Council Minutes, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 408)
- Admissions-Fuller, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 409)
- Aeronautical Engineering-Truitt, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 410)
- Agriculture-Dietrick, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 411)
- Agricultural Economics-Love, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 412)
- Agricultural Engineering-Swink, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 413)
- Agricultural Experiment Station-Young, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 414)
- Agricultural Extension Service, 1955-1958 (Box 12, Folder 415)
- Agronomy, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 416)
- American Association of University Professors, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 417)
- American Council on Education, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 418)
- Animal Husbandry-Litton, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 419)
- Applied Science and Business Administration-Johnston, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 420)
- Applied Mechanics-Pletta, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 421)
- Architecture-Currie, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 422)
- Association of Virginia Colleges, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 423)
- Athletic Council, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 424)
- Atomic Energy, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 425a-c)
- Biochemistry and Nutrition-Engel, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 426)
- Biology-Orcutt, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 427)
- Business Administration, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 428)
- C, General, 1954-1958 (Box 12, Folder 429)
- Chemistry-Watson, 1956-1958 (Box 12, Folder 430)
- Civil Engineering-Morris, 1956-1958 (Box 12, Folder 431)
- Deans, 1956-1958 (Box 12, Folder 432)
- Deans of Southern Graduate Schools, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 433)
- Director of Development-Fisher, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 434)
- Electrical Engineering-Widener, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 435)
- Engineering and Architecture-Whittemore, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 436)
- Faculty, Committee on Graduate Forums, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 437)
- Faculty, Committee on Instruction, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 438)
- Faculty, Count, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 439)
- Faculty, Listing and Salary, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 440)
- Faculty, Promotions, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 441)
- Faculty, Resignations, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 442)
- Faculty, Retirements, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 443)
- Ford Foundation Grant-Fisher, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 444)
- Ford Foundation Press Releases, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 445)
- Foreign Students, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 446)
- Geology-Cooper, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 447)
- Grade Percentages, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 448)
- Guidance and Placement-Cato, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 449)
- Home Economics-Tate, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 450)
- Horticulture-Judkins, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 451)
- I, General, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 452)
- Inauguration, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 453)
- Industrial Engineering-Manning, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 454)
- Institute of International Education, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 455)
- Invitations, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 456)
- Junior Colleges, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 457)
- K, General, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 458)
- L, General, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 459)
- Labor Survey of Counties Surrounding VPI, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 460)
- Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 461)
- Langley Field, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 462)
- M, General, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 463)
- Mechanical Engineering-Jones, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 464)
- Metallurgical Engineering-Eckel, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 465)
- Military-Devine, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 466)
- N, General, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 467)
- National Institute of Health, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 468)
- National Science Foundation, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 469)
- Natural Resource Conservation Short Course, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 470)
- O, General, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 471)
- P, General, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 472)
- Personnel-Evans, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 473)
- Pest Control Operators Banquet, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 474)
- Philosophy and Religion-Grover, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 475)
- Physics-Hahn, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 476)
- Plant Pathology and Physiology, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 477)
- Poultry Husbandry-Howes, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 478)
- President-Newman, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 479)
- Public Relations-McNeil, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 480)
- Purchasing Agent-Swink, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 481)
- Q, General, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 482)
- Questionnaire (2 folders), 1958 (Box 13, Folder 483a-b)
- R, General, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 484)
- Radford College-Marin, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 485)
- Regional Advisory Council on Nuclear Energy (3 folders), 1958 (Box 13, Folder 486a-c)
- Registrar-Slusher, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 487)
- S, General, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 488)
- Salary Information, 1957-1958 (Box 13, Folder 489)
- Scholarships at VPI, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 490)
- Science Advisory Committee (2 folders), 1958 (Box 13, Folder 491a-b)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 492)
- Southern Association of Land-Grant Colleges and Universities, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 493)
- Southern Regional Education Board (2 folders), 1957-1958 (Box 13, Folder 494a-b)
- State Board of Education, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 495)
- State Council on Higher Education (3 folders), 1958 (Box 13, Folder 496a-c)
- State Fair Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 13, Folder 497)
- Statistics-Harshbarger, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 498)
- Student Affairs, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 499)
- Summer Institute for High School Science Teachers, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 500)
- Symposium on Statistics, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 501)
- T, General, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 502)
- Technical Institute, Roanoke, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 503)
- Television, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 504)
- University Club, 1957-1958 (Box 13, Folder 505)
- V, General, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 506)
- Virginia Academy of Science, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 507)
- Virginia Educational Association, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 508)
- Virginia Farm Bureau Federation, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 509)
- Virginia Junior Academy of Science, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 510)
- Vocational Education, 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 511)
- W, General, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 512)
- Woodrow Wilson Fellowship Program, 1955-1958 (Box 14, Folder 513)
- YMCA, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 514)
- A, General, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 515)
- Academic Council Minutes, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 516)
- Accreditation, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 517)
- Admissions-Farrier, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 518)
- Advisory Board on the Budget, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 519)
- Aeronautical Engineering-Truit, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 520)
- Agriculture-Dietrick, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 521)
- Agricultural Engineering-Swink, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 522)
- Agricultural Experiment Station Young, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 523)
- Agronomy-Dunton, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 524)
- Alumni Association-Oliver, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 525)
- American Association of Land-Grant Colleges and Universities, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 526)
- American Association of University Professors, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 527)
- American Council on Education, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 528)
- American Physical Society, Southeast Section, 1952-1959 (Box 14, Folder 529)
- Animal Husbandry-Litton, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 530)
- Applied Mechanics-Pletta, 1957-1959 (Box 14, Folder 531)
- Applied Science and Business Administration, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 532)
- Architecture-Currie, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 533)
- Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 534)
- Association of Virginia Colleges, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 535)
- Athletic Council, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 536)
- Atomic Energy Commission, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 537)
- B, General, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 538)
- Biology-Orcutt, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 539)
- Business Administration-Miller, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 540)
- Business Manager-Cassell, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 541)
- C, General, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 542)
- Chemical Engineering-Bull, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 543)
- Chemistry-Krug, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 544)
- Chinese Scholars, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 545)
- Civil Engineering-Morris, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 546)
- College Policy, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 547)
- Committee on Admission by Examination and with Advanced Standing, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 548)
- Co-operative Engineering-Cain, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 549)
- Dairy Science-Graf, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 550)
- Danforth Foundation, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 551)
- Danville Branch-Taylor, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 552)
- Director of Development-Fisher, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 553)
- Electrical Engineering-Powley, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 554)
- Engineering and Architecture-Whittemore, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 555)
- English and Foreign Languages-Harrison, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 556)
- Entomology-Grayson, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 557)
- Exchange Visitors Program, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 558)
- F, General, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 559)
- Faculty Appointments, Agriculture, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 560)
- Faculty Appointments, Applied Science and Business Administration, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 561)
- Faculty Appointments, Engineering and Architecture, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 562)
- Faculty Committee on Graduate Forums, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 563)
- Faculty Committee on Instruction, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 564)
- Faculty Leaves of Absence, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 565)
- Faculty Listing (2 folders), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 566a-b)
- Faculty Outside Consulting, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 567)
- Faculty Promotions, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 568)
- Faculty Resignations, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 569)
- Ford Foundation, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 570)
- G, General, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 571)
- Geology-Cooper, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 572)
- Grade Percentages, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 573)
- Graphics-Castleman, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 574)
- Greenbriar Conference, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 575)
- Guidance and Placement-Cato, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 576)
- H, General, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 577)
- Health Education and Welfare, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 578)
- Home Economics-Harper, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 579)
- Honors Curriculum, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 580)
- Horticulture-Judkins, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 581)
- I, General, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 582)
- Inauguration, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 583)
- Industrial Engineering-Manning, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 584)
- Institute of International Education, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 585)
- Insurance and Tax Information, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 586)
- International Education and Exchange Conference, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 587)
- Invitations, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 588)
- J, General, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 589)
- Joint Office of Institutional Research, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 590)
- K, General, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 591)
- L, General, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 592)
- Langley Field, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 593)
- Library-Robb, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 594)
- Lynchburg Foundry, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 595)
- M, General, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 596)
- Mathematics-Hatcher, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 597)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 598)
- Metallurgical Engineering-Eckel, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 599)
- Military-Devine, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 600)
- Mining Engineering-Holland, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 601)
- N, General, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 602)
- National Education Association, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 603)
- National Science Foundation (4 folders), 1959 (Box 15, Folder 604a-d)
- P, General, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 605)
- Personnel-Evans, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 606)
- Pest Control Operator's Short Course, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 607)
- Physics-Hahn, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 608)
- President-Newman, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 609)
- Publications Listed, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 610)
- Public Relations-McNeil, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 611)
- Questionnaires (4 folders), 1959 (Box 15, Folder 612a-d)
- R, General, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 613)
- Redstone Arsenal, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 615)
- Regional Advisory Council on Nuclear Energy (2 folders), 1959 (Box 15, Folder 616a-b)
- Registrar-Slusher, 1958-1959 (Box 15, Folder 617)
- Religious Activities Committee, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 618)
- Rotary (3 folders), 1959 (Box 15, Folder 619a-c)
- S, General, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 620)
- Salary Listing, 1958-1959 (Box 15, Folder 621)
- Speeches, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 622)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 623)
- Southern Regional Education Board (3 folders), 1959 (Box 15, Folder 624a-c)
- State Advisory Committee on Nuclear Energy, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 625)
- State Board of Education, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 626)
- State Council on Higher Education (2 folders), 1959 (Box 15, Folder 627a-b)
- State Fair Committee, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 628)
- Statistics-Harshbarger, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 629)
- Student Activities Committee, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 630)
- Student Affairs (2 folders), 1959 (Box 16, Folder 631a-b)
- Science Institute for High School Science Teachers-Krug, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 632)
- Summer School, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 633)
- Superior Student Letter (3 folders), 1959 (Box 16, Folder 634a-c)
- Symposium, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 635)
- University Club, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 636)
- Virginia Academy of Science, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 637)
- Virginia Educational Association, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 638)
- Vocational Education-Sanders (3 folders), 1959 (Box 16, Folder 639a-c)
- VPI "Its Aims, Needs, and Future" Program, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 640)
- W, General, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 641)
- Y, General, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 642)
- YMCA-Payne (2 folders), 1959 (Box 16, Folder 643)
- A, General, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 644)
- Academic Council, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 645)
- Accreditation, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 646)
- Admissions-Farrier, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 647)
- Agriculture-Dietrick, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 648)
- Agricultural Experiment Station-Young, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 649)
- Agricultural Extension Service-Dietrick, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 650)
- Agronomy-Dunton, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 651)
- Alumni Association, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 652)
- American Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 653)
- American Association of University Professors, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 654)
- American Council on Education, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 655)
- American Institute of Planners, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 656)
- Animal Husbandry-Litton, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 657)
- Applied Science and Business Administration-Johnston, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 658)
- Athletic Association-Moseley, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 659)
- Atomic Energy Commission, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 660)
- B, General, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 661)
- Biochemistry and Nutrition-Engel, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 662)
- Biology-Orcutt, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 663)